<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Fabric on Ram&#39;s Website</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/fabric/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fabric on Ram&#39;s Website</description>
    <image>
      <title>Ram&#39;s Website</title>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.134.3</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/fabric/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hyperledger Fabric Deployment — How We Aced it from Testing to Production</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2022-09-26-fabric-from-development-to-production/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2022-09-26-fabric-from-development-to-production/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;You’ve set up your Dev environment, developed your chaincode, designed some decent looking UIs, and passed all your tests to get everything up &amp;amp; running locally. Now what? Is that everything you ever wanted? Of course not! You shouldn’t be satisfied at all. You need to do more. Your next target ought to be to scale the network and stimulate a production-level environment. Added to that, you should also focus on adding multiple orderers, organizations with their own peers and CAs, and try testing it on multiple machines.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hitachi Shifts to Paperless, Secure Procurement Contracts with Hyperledger Fabric</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2022-09-07-hitachi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2022-09-07-hitachi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read the full case study &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.hyperledger.org/learn/publications/hitachi-case-study&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Paper pushing. It’s synonymous with tedious, slow processes. Yet often, the pushed paper is vital to a company’s business. And contracts are especially important paper.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But digitizing a contract process isn’t as simple as it sounds. As the contract moves between parties, there’s a risk of tampering. Or mismanaging version control.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many companies continue to use paper for their contracting processes to maintain security and trust. The procurement divisions of Hitachi, Ltd. were no different.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
