<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>World Economics on Ram&#39;s Website</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/world-economics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in World Economics on Ram&#39;s Website</description>
    <image>
      <title>Ram&#39;s Website</title>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.134.3</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/world-economics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Risk of Global Recession in 2023 Rises Amid Simultaneous Rate Hikes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2022-10-15-risk-of-global-recession-in-2023-rises-amid-simultaneous-rate-hikes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2022-10-15-risk-of-global-recession-in-2023-rises-amid-simultaneous-rate-hikes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;risk-of-global-recession-in-2023-rises-amid-simultaneous-rate-hikes&#34;&gt;Risk of Global Recession in 2023 Rises Amid Simultaneous Rate Hikes&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As central banks across the world simultaneously hike interest rates in response to inflation, the world may be edging toward a global recession in 2023 and a string of financial crises in emerging market and developing economies that would do them lasting harm, according to a comprehensive new study by the World Bank.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Central banks around the world have been raising interest rates this year with a degree of synchronicity not seen over the past five decades—a trend that is likely to continue well into next year, according to the report. Yet the currently expected trajectory of interest-rate increases and other policy actions may not be sufficient to bring global inflation back down to levels seen before the pandemic. Investors expect central banks to raise global monetary-policy rates to almost 4 percent through 2023—an increase of more than 2 percentage points over their 2021 average.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
